[
    {
        "question": "بروك",
        "response": "ب ر و ك"
    },
    {
        "question": "فيفي",
        "response": "ف ي ف ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "لوفي",
        "response": "ل و ف ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "زورو",
        "response": "ز و ر و"
    },
    {
        "question": "سانجي",
        "response": "س ا ن ج ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "نامي",
        "response": "ن ا م ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "روبين",
        "response": "ر و ب ي ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوسوب",
        "response": "ا و س و ب"
    },
    {
        "question": "فرانكي",
        "response": "ف ر ا ن ك ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "جيمبي",
        "response": "ج ي م ب ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "لاكسس",
        "response": "ل ا ك س س"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايرين",
        "response": "ا ي ر ي ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "ماي",
        "response": "م ا ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "جيغن",
        "response": "ج ي غ ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "هشيراما",
        "response": "ه ش ي ر ا م ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "روك لي",
        "response": "ر و ك ل ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "استا",
        "response": "ا س ت ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "لاو",
        "response": "ل ا و"
    },
    {
        "question": "روجر",
        "response": "ر و ج ر"
    },
    {
        "question": "جيرايا",
        "response": "ج ي ر ا ي ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "لولوش",
        "response": "ل و ل و ش"
    },
    {
        "question": "لايت",
        "response": "ل ا ي ت"
    },
    {
        "question": "ال",
        "response": "ا ل"
    },
    {
        "question": "موب",
        "response": "م و ب"
    },
    {
        "question": "ريكا",
        "response": "ر ي ك ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاغويا",
        "response": "ك ا غ و ي ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "شينرا",
        "response": "ش ي ن ر ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "فيفي",
        "response": "ف ي ف ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "واكاسا",
        "response": "و ا ك ا س ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "سانجي",
        "response": "س ا ن ج ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "اكاشي",
        "response": "ا ك ا ش ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوميكو",
        "response": "ي و م ي ك و"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثورز",
        "response": "ث و ر ز"
    },
    {
        "question": "عبدول",
        "response": "ع ب د و ل"
    },
    {
        "question": "ويليام",
        "response": "و ي ل ي ا م"
    },
    {
        "question": "اكامي",
        "response": "ا ك ا م ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "مادارا",
        "response": "م ا د ا ر ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "جوزيف",
        "response": "ج و ز ي ف"
    },
    {
        "question": "كينغ",
        "response": "ك ي ن غ"
    },
    {
        "question": "لاك",
        "response": "ل ا ك"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيناتا",
        "response": "ه ي ن ا ت ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كانيكي",
        "response": "ك ا ن ي ك ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كوراما",
        "response": "ك و ر ا م ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيسامي",
        "response": "ك ي س ا م ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيساكي",
        "response": "ك ي س ا ك ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيسكي",
        "response": "ك ي س ك ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "غوكو",
        "response": "غ و ك و"
    },
    {
        "question": "ليفاي",
        "response": "ل ي ف ا ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيراكو",
        "response": "ه ي ر ا ك و"
    },
    {
        "question": "روكيا",
        "response": "ر و ك ي ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاناو",
        "response": "ك ا ن ا و"
    },
    {
        "question": "دازاي",
        "response": "د ا ز ا ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيروتو",
        "response": "ك ي ر و ت و"
    },
    {
        "question": "هوكس",
        "response": "ه و ك س"
    },
    {
        "question": "ناغاتو",
        "response": "ن ا غ ا ت و"
    },
    {
        "question": "غاي",
        "response": "غ ا ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "مارلين",
        "response": "م ا ر ل ي ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميراجين",
        "response": "م ي ر ا ج ي ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "زورو",
        "response": "ز و ر و"
    },
    {
        "question": "كايدو",
        "response": "ك ا ي د و"
    },
    {
        "question": "كورابيكا",
        "response": "ك و ر ا ب ي ك ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "فيجيتا",
        "response": "ف ي ج ي ت ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "راينر",
        "response": "ر ا ي ن ر"
    },
    {
        "question": "سوكونا",
        "response": "س و ك و ن ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيزارو",
        "response": "ك ي ز ا ر و"
    },
    {
        "question": "ارثر",
        "response": "ا ر ث ر"
    },
    {
        "question": "روبين",
        "response": "ر و ب ي ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "تسونادي",
        "response": "ت س و ن ا د ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "زابزو",
        "response": "ز ا ب ز و"
    },
    {
        "question": "زابوزا",
        "response": "ز ا ب و ز ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيستوريا",
        "response": "ه ي س ت و ر ي ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوليوس",
        "response": "ي و ل ي و س"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيزوكو",
        "response": "ن ي ز و ك و"
    },
    {
        "question": "ناخت",
        "response": "ن ا خ ت"
    },
    {
        "question": "زاك",
        "response": "ز ا ك"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيلربي",
        "response": "ك ي ل ر ب ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسكانور",
        "response": "ا س ك ا ن و ر"
    },
    {
        "question": "شويفيو",
        "response": "ش و ي ف ي و"
    },
    {
        "question": "غيو",
        "response": "غ ي و"
    },
    {
        "question": "جوناثان",
        "response": "ج و ن ا ث ا ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميريوم",
        "response": "م ي ر ي و م"
    },
    {
        "question": "اول مايت",
        "response": "ا و ل م ا ي ت"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيدان",
        "response": "ه ي د ا ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "لوفي",
        "response": "ل و ف ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوهان",
        "response": "ي و ه ا ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "رين",
        "response": "ر ي ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "كورو",
        "response": "ك و ر و"
    },
    {
        "question": "شانكس",
        "response": "ش ا ن ك س"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاكاشي",
        "response": "ك ا ك ا ش ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "لوتشي",
        "response": "ل و ت ش ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كوين",
        "response": "ك و ي ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "هوري",
        "response": "ه و ر ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "شيسوي",
        "response": "ش ي س و ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ياماتو",
        "response": "ي ا م ا ت و"
    },
    {
        "question": "ياماموتو",
        "response": "ي ا م ا م و ت و"
    },
    {
        "question": "كونان",
        "response": "ك و ن ا ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "نير",
        "response": "ن ي ر"
    },
    {
        "question": "شينوبو",
        "response": "ش ي ن و ب و"
    },
    {
        "question": "سانيمي",
        "response": "س ا ن ي م ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوباناي",
        "response": "ا و ب ا ن ا ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "رينغوكو",
        "response": "ر ي ن غ و ك و"
    },
    {
        "question": "غيومي",
        "response": "غ ي و م ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاناي",
        "response": "ك ا ن ا ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "نويل",
        "response": "ن و ي ل"
    },
    {
        "question": "يامي",
        "response": "ي ا م ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "شيغاراكي",
        "response": "ش ي غ ا ر ا ك ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "شوتو",
        "response": "ش و ت و"
    },
    {
        "question": "باكوغو",
        "response": "ب ا ك و غ و"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميدوريا",
        "response": "م ي د و ر ي ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ياتو",
        "response": "ي ا ت و"
    },
    {
        "question": "تويا",
        "response": "ت و ي ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوتاما",
        "response": "ا و ت ا م ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "جوتارو",
        "response": "ج و ت ا ر و"
    },
    {
        "question": "ديو",
        "response": "د ي و"
    },
    {
        "question": "دراغون",
        "response": "د ر ا غ و ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "سابو",
        "response": "س ا ب و"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايس",
        "response": "ا ي س"
    },
    {
        "question": "غارب",
        "response": "غ ا ر ب"
    },
    {
        "question": "هاك",
        "response": "ه ا ك"
    },
    {
        "question": "بان",
        "response": "ب ا ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "يونا",
        "response": "ي و ن ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميليوداس",
        "response": "م ي ل ي و د ا س"
    },
    {
        "question": "باجي",
        "response": "ب ا ج ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كروكودايل",
        "response": "ك ر و ك و د ا ي ل"
    },
    {
        "question": "دوفلامينغو",
        "response": "د و ف ل ا م ي ن غ و"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميهوك",
        "response": "م ي ه و ك"
    },
    {
        "question": "دابي",
        "response": "د ا ب ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميغومي",
        "response": "م ي غ و م ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايتادوري",
        "response": "ا ي ت ا د و ر ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوجي",
        "response": "ي و ج ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "نوبارا",
        "response": "ن و ب ا ر ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "سينكو",
        "response": "س ي ن ك و"
    },
    {
        "question": "غون",
        "response": "غ و ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيلوا",
        "response": "ك ي ل و ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميريوم",
        "response": "م ي ر ي و م"
    },
    {
        "question": "سيلفا",
        "response": "س ي ل ف ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هانزو",
        "response": "ه ا ن ز و"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوبيتو",
        "response": "ا و ب ي ت و"
    },
    {
        "question": "توغا",
        "response": "ت و غ ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "سابيتو",
        "response": "س ا ب ي ت و"
    },
    {
        "question": "اريما",
        "response": "ا ر ي م ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "نورمان",
        "response": "ن و ر م ا ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "راي",
        "response": "ر ا ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوسوب",
        "response": "ي و س و ب"
    },
    {
        "question": "شيكامارو",
        "response": "ش ي ك ا م ا ر و"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوسوب",
        "response": "ا و س و ب"
    },
    {
        "question": "اندرا",
        "response": "ا ن د ر ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "يونا",
        "response": "ي و ن ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "شوتو",
        "response": "ش و ت و"
    },
    {
        "question": "ناتسو",
        "response": "ن ا ت س و"
    },
    {
        "question": "لوسي",
        "response": "ل و س ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "هابي",
        "response": "ه ا ب ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "زيريف",
        "response": "ز ي ر ي ف"
    },
    {
        "question": "نويل",
        "response": "ن و ي ل"
    },
    {
        "question": "راي",
        "response": "ر ا ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "اودين",
        "response": "ا و د ي ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايدوارد",
        "response": "ا ي د و ا ر د"
    },
    {
        "question": "تيتش",
        "response": "ت ي ت ش"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللحية السوداء",
        "response": "ا ل ل ح ي ة ا ل س و د ا ء"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللحية البيضاء",
        "response": "ا ل ل ح ي ة ا ل ب ي ض ا ء"
    },
    {
        "question": "زيرو تو",
        "response": "ز ي ر و ت و"
    },
    {
        "question": "نويل",
        "response": "ن و ي ل"
    },
    {
        "question": "اودين",
        "response": "ا و د ي ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "كوين",
        "response": "ك و ي ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايتاتشي",
        "response": "ا ي ت ا ت ش ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايتاشي",
        "response": "ا ي ت ا ش ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "شيسوي",
        "response": "ش ي س و ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ساسكي",
        "response": "س ا س ك ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "مادارا",
        "response": "م ا د ا ر ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "بياكويا",
        "response": "ا ك ا ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "سينتشي",
        "response": "س ي ن ت ش ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "تاكيميتشي",
        "response": "ت ا ك ي م ي ت ش ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاتسورا",
        "response": "ك ا ت س و ر ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "جينتوكي",
        "response": "ج ي ن ت و ك ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاتاكوري",
        "response": "ك ا ت ا ك و ر ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "اكاينو",
        "response": "ا ك ا ي ن و"
    },
    {
        "question": "بيغ مام",
        "response": "ب ي غ م ا م"
    },
    {
        "question": "لينلين",
        "response": "ل ي ن ل ي ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوكيجي",
        "response": "ا و ك ي ج ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "نانامي",
        "response": "ن ا ن ا م ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ماهيتو",
        "response": "م ا ه ي ت و"
    },
    {
        "question": "موهيتو",
        "response": "م و ه ي ت و"
    },
    {
        "question": "ديو",
        "response": "د ي و"
    },
    {
        "question": "ساي",
        "response": "س ا ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كوشينا",
        "response": "ك و ش ي ن ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ساكورا",
        "response": "س ا ك و ر ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيناتا",
        "response": "ه ي ن ا ت ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميهوك",
        "response": "م ي ه و ك"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميدوريا",
        "response": "م ي د و ر ي ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "تانجيرو",
        "response": "ت ا ن ج ي ر و"
    },
    {
        "question": "زينتسو",
        "response": "ز ي ن ت س و"
    },
    {
        "question": "اينوسكي",
        "response": "ا ي ن و س ك ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيزوكو",
        "response": "ن ي ز و ك و"
    },
    {
        "question": "اينوي",
        "response": "ا ي ن و ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيسوكا",
        "response": "ه ي س و ك ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كرولو",
        "response": "ك ر و ل و"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميليوداس",
        "response": "م ي ل ي و د ا س"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاناو",
        "response": "ك ا ن ا و"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاناي",
        "response": "ك ا ن ا ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "غوجيتا",
        "response": "غ و ج ي ت ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "زيك",
        "response": "ز ي ك"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميناتو",
        "response": "م ي ن ا ت و"
    },
    {
        "question": "نورمان",
        "response": "ن و ر م ا ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "شيريو",
        "response": "ش ي ر ي و"
    },
    {
        "question": "جاك",
        "response": "ج ا ك"
    },
    {
        "question": "كايتو كيد",
        "response": "ك ا ي ت و ك ي د"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيد",
        "response": "ك ي د"
    },
    {
        "question": "رينغوكو",
        "response": "ر ي ن غ و ك و"
    },
    {
        "question": "توبيراما",
        "response": "ت و ب ي ر ا م ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "لابون",
        "response": "ل ا ب و ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "ليون",
        "response": "ل ي و ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاواكي",
        "response": "ك ا و ا ك ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "شارلوك هولمز",
        "response": "ش ا ر ل و ك ه و ل م ز"
    },
    {
        "question": "شارلوك",
        "response": "ش ا ر ل و ك"
    },
    {
        "question": "كورو",
        "response": "ك و ر و"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوكي",
        "response": "ا و ك ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "تو",
        "response": "ت و"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوسين",
        "response": "ا و س ي ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيوكاي",
        "response": "ك ي و ك ا ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كانكي",
        "response": "ك ا ن ك ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "زاراكي",
        "response": "ز ا ر ا ك ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ساسكي",
        "response": "س ا س ك ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ساكورا",
        "response": "س ا ك و ر ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميتسكي",
        "response": "م ي ت س ك ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "سارادا",
        "response": "س ا ر ا د ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ناروتو",
        "response": "ن ا ر و ت و"
    },
    {
        "question": "بوروتو",
        "response": "ب و ر و ت و"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميتسوبيشي",
        "response": "م ي ت س و ب ي ش ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميتسوري",
        "response": "م ي ت س و ر ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوتا",
        "response": "ي و ت ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "تويا",
        "response": "ت و ي ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ريم",
        "response": "ر ي م"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميكا",
        "response": "م ي ك ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميكايلا",
        "response": "م ي ك ا ي ل ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "نامي",
        "response": "ن ا م ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "راينر",
        "response": "ر ا ي ن ر"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيترو",
        "response": "ن ي ت ر و"
    },
    {
        "question": "لوسي",
        "response": "ل و س ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "سابو",
        "response": "س ا ب و"
    },
    {
        "question": "يامي",
        "response": "ي ا م ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "زينو",
        "response": "ز ي ن و"
    },
    {
        "question": "فيونا",
        "response": "ف ي و ن ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ديدارا",
        "response": "د ي د ا ر ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ريم",
        "response": "ر ي م"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميكا",
        "response": "م ي ك ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميكايلا",
        "response": "م ي ك ا ي ل ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "نامي",
        "response": "ن ا م ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "راينر",
        "response": "ر ا ي ن ر"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيترو",
        "response": "ن ي ت ر و"
    },
    {
        "question": "لوسي",
        "response": "ل و س ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "سابو",
        "response": "س ا ب و"
    },
    {
        "question": "يامي",
        "response": "ي ا م ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "زينو",
        "response": "ز ي ن و"
    },
    {
        "question": "فيونا",
        "response": "ف ي و ن ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ديدارا",
        "response": "د ي د ا ر ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ستارك",
        "response": "س ت ا ر ك"
    },
    {
        "question": "غوهان",
        "response": "غ و ه ا ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيجي",
        "response": "ن ي ج ي"
    },
        {
        "question": "زيريف",
        "response": "ز ي ر ي ف"
    },
    {
        "question": "يونو",
        "response": "ي و ن و"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميريليونا",
        "response": "م ي ر ي ل ي و ن ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ران",
        "response": "ر ا ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "ماركو",
        "response": "م ا ر ك و"
    },
    {
        "question": "ويس",
        "response": "و ي س"
    },
    {
        "question": "فيجيتا",
        "response": "ف ي ج ي ت ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "فريزا",
        "response": "ف ر ي ز ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيوكاي",
        "response": "ك ي و ك ا ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "غوثر",
        "response": "غ و ث ر"
    },
    {
        "question": "سايتاما",
        "response": "س ا ي ت ا م ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "جينوس",
        "response": "ج ي ن و س"
    },
    {
        "question": "غارو",
        "response": "غ ا ر و"
    },
    {
        "question": "زيلدريس",
        "response": "ز ي ل د ر ي س"
    },
    {
        "question": "شنايدر",
        "response": "ش ن ا ي د ر"
    },
    {
        "question": "ارشر",
        "response": "ا ر ش ر"
    },
    {
        "question": "غاتس",
        "response": "غ ا ت س"
    },
    {
        "question": "غريفيث",
        "response": "غ ر ي ف ي ث"
    },
    {
        "question": "شيسوي",
        "response": "ش ي س و ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايروين",
        "response": "ا ي ر و ي ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميكاسا",
        "response": "م ي ك ا س ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ليفاي",
        "response": "ل ي ف ا ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "هوك",
        "response": "ه و ك"
    },
    {
        "question": "بين بيكمان",
        "response": "ب ي ن ب ي ك م ا ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيلوا",
        "response": "ك ي ل و ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "اني",
        "response": "ا ن ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميكاسا",
        "response": "م ي ك ا س ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هانجي",
        "response": "ه ا ن ج ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ساشا",
        "response": "س ا ش ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كايدو",
        "response": "ك ا ي د و"
    },
    {
        "question": "ارتوريا",
        "response": "ا ر ت و ر ي ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "الوكا",
        "response": "ا ل و ك ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "نوبارا",
        "response": "ن و ب ا ر ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "باين",
        "response": "ب ا ي ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "موزان",
        "response": "م و ز ا ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "دوفلامينغو",
        "response": "د و ف ل ا م ي ن غ و"
    },
    {
        "question": "لويد",
        "response": "ل و ي د"
    },
    {
        "question": "انيا",
        "response": "ا ن ي ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميليوداس",
        "response": "م ي ل ي و د ا س"
    },
    {
        "question": "تاكيميتشي",
        "response": "ت ا ك ي م ي ت ش ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوبيتو",
        "response": "ا و ب ي ت و"
    },
    {
        "question": "بيلامي",
        "response": "ب ي ل ا م ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ديانا",
        "response": "د ي ا ن ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "بان",
        "response": "ب ا ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوكابي",
        "response": "ا و ك ا ب ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "تسونا",
        "response": "ت س و ن ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "فيتان",
        "response": "ف ي ت ا ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "يور",
        "response": "ي و ر"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيرو",
        "response": "ه ي ر و"
    },
    {
        "question": "جوزو",
        "response": "ج و ز و"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوريتشي",
        "response": "ي و ر ي ت ش ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "يورويتشي",
        "response": "ي و ر و ي ت ش ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "هاناكو",
        "response": "ه ا ن ا ك و"
    },
    {
        "question": "مايكي",
        "response": "م ا ي ك ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "فايوليت",
        "response": "ف ا ي و ل ي ت"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيوراك",
        "response": "ك ي و ر ا ك"
    },
    {
        "question": "ارمين",
        "response": "ا ر م ي ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "البيرت",
        "response": "ا ل ب ي ر ت"
    },
    {
        "question": "توكا",
        "response": "ت و ك ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "باكوغا",
        "response": "ب ا ك و غ ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيوكاي",
        "response": "ك ي و ك ا ي"
    }
]
